

Email maciekmp@gmail.com

CONTACT Phone 881 500 058

Website http://maciejplusa.com/

LOCATION Poland

City Szczecin

Languages English

Smooth communication, reading and writing documentation.

GitHub github.com/

PROFILES Facebook fb.me/maciekmp

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/maciejplusa

CodePen codepen.io/maciekmp/

ABOUT ME

From an early age I am passionate about technology. I've been programming commercially for 8 years. I derive pleasure from effective work on internet applications. I use the latest technology and standards. In my spare time I am driving a hybrid car.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Content coach and tutor at Infoshare Academy

One of the largest companies organizing training in Szczecin. Courses in various fields focus around practical classes.

Work as a substantive expert on selected topics from the course for frontend developers.

Preparing presentations and exercises for classes.

Taking care of the whole course: work organization, task verification, role of manager's project and technical lead.

2013 TILL 2017

Senior Software Developer / Fullstack at Tidio

Tidio Chat is a solution based on the live chat platform for communication with clients. The innovative approach allowed to occupy a high position on the market of this type of messengers.

Responsibility and work on every key element of a new project.

Building from scratch a new version of the panel for operators using new technologies.

Working with a widget loaded on hundreds of thousands of pages. The use of new architecture and optimization in all available ways.

Construction and development of new functions.

Everyday work using the SCRUM methodology.

2012-01 TILL 2012-12

Middle Software Developer at Abee

Website construction platform based on the WordPress engine.

Implementing new websites on the WordPress platform.

Building plugins based on good practices with the WordPress API.

Creating a system that generates copies of subsequent pages with all elements (database, files, data).

Creating a new interface with a simple website support in the form of a plugin.

2011 TILL 2012

Web Software Developer at ii4b

An innovative company implementing solutions based on big data and facebook applications.

Work on the concept of new products and applications produced by the company.

Creating new websites related to company identification.

Construction of new applications on the Facebook platform.

Cooperation on a prototype using Kinect technology.

2010 TILL 2011

Middle Software Developer at nTeam

A company that develops and develops websites for real estate offices using the proprietary CMS system that works with the largest systems on the market to store real estate offers.

Construction of new websites for real estate offices with the use of proprietary CMS.

Expansion of existing websites with new modules and requirements.

Creating new modules to meet customer expectations.

2010 TILL 2010

Junior Software Developer at FitPlus

Social Startup aggregating information about exercises performed with the tracking function of training plans.

Creating a social website from scratch.

Construction of the entire interface composed of many screens.

UX tests on potential users.

EDUCATION

2008 TILL 2013

West Pomeranian University of Technology

Engineering: Informatics

Awards

DIGE NINJA CONTEST
2013

Dike

The best graph visualization application using the d3.js library.

THE BEST COMPUTER GAME 2010

ZUT - Department of Multimedia

Second place for the best computer game. A game based on turn-based gameplay using 3D tank models.

STARTUP WEEKEND WARSAW 2010

Startup Weekend

Second place for the project using Kinect technology in public advertising.

Frontend Development (Master): Application architecture, React, HTML5, CSS, Less, JavaScript, jQuery, Webpack

Backend Development (Regular): PHP, Laravel, MySQL, MongoDB, Linux

Web Performance (Senior): Website Speed, SEO, CDN

SKILLS

Soft skills: Work organization focusing on process optimization, Running projects and teams at medium scale, Making development decisions, managing resources, Recruitment and evaluation of employees

General Tools: JetBrains IDE software, Google Chrome Developer Tools, Vagrant, Go, Konsola Linux, Apache/Nginx

Interests

Privately: New technologies, Efficiency and optimization of work, Xbox, bartending